MICHAEL ROSENGART: Right now, I'm here with two personal trainers, Ryan Regensburg and Jonesy and we're doing some renegade rows.
So, what I want you to do is go ahead and get into a push up position with two dumbbells in your hands, whereas Ryan's going to show us later on a little variation for it.
Jonesy's here in a push up position.
And what you're going to do is you're going to pull one of the dumbbells up into your rib cage, shifting your weight back and forth.
Now, if you're just starting on this, you may want to work with really wide feet.
That will give you more balance and support as you perform, alright?
At the same time, if you want a little bit more of a challenge, bring your feet closer together as you work.
Exhale as you pull up and you're going to feel that you really get to use your abdominals and your obliques as you go back and forth.
Ryan, go ahead and get down.
And Ryan's going to do a one-handed renegade row.
So, basically, he's just going to work one side at a time.
The hand on the ground will give him a little more support and will make it a little easier.
And then once he does five, he's just going to switch over to the other side.
Again, for this workout, we're working for fifteen to twenty reps and another variation that I want you to work on or consider if you can do it, is a push up renegade row like Jonesy's doing here.
Each time you're going down, you're going to do a push up and then come back up.
It helps for a couple of different reasons, it helps again, to condition the chest but it also helps to stretch up--stretch out the anterior side of your shoulders which then allows you to get a deeper row.
Alright.
Good.
And then once you've done with fifteen or twenty reps, grab some water, meet us on the next exercise in the next clip.